jungledealsandsteals.com 2019-05-09

# Privacy Policy | Jungle Deals and Steals

The privacy of our visitors is extremely important. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected and how it is used.

Your use of this site, in any and all forms, constitutes an acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

 **1\. Log Files**

Like many other websites, we use log files which track:

  * Internet Protocol addresses (IP)
  * Types of browser
  * Internet Service Provider (ISP)
  * Date and time stamp
  * Referring and exit pages
  * Number of clicks

None of this information is linked to anything that is personally identifiable, and it is only used to provide a better user experience.

 **2\. Cookies**

Some of my advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on my site. My advertising partners include, but are not limited to, Amazon and its Affiliates.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks sponsor advertisements and links on Jungle Deals & Steals that are sent directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Jungle Deals & Steals has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt out of certain practices. Jungle Deals & Steals’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

 **3\. Personal Information**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **4\. Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

In compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 18 years old or older.

 **5\. External Links**

While Jungle Deals & Steals is highly selective about which sites we provide links to, we do not control these web sites, nor do we endorse or otherwise accept responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on third party sites.

 **6\. Other**

Users might be asked to subscribe to our newsletter by providing name and email address to receive communication from Jungle Deals & Steals. We use a secure op-in subscription system and we reserve the right to contact subscribers with information related to this website and blog. Subscribers may unsubscribe anytime and every email delivered will contain an “Unsubscribe” link.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://jungledealsandsteals.com/contact/).

Last Updated: July 8, 2011
